this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother
ace to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down
along the way he ran into bucky as well as former baroque works agents mr. three and mr. two
together they fell from level three down to level four
hot hot hot hot hot hot that food smells so good hot hot hot hot oh boy i can't wait for yummy food time
uh
aaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhh!
it's time to put an end to your buffoonery once and for all
boy
who are you??
it's megillon!!!
what?!
I've got you now
you criminal scum!!!!
mighty magellan
bon clay
Hey, Bugs out!
Oh crap, I gotta get out of here!
It's truly quite hot down here.
Warden, wait, please!
Give us a second!
Don't start fighting it!
Everyone, clear out!
The warden's poison will get us too!
You suck!
I was finally gonna make it to all that awesome-smelling food over there!
I'm hot, I'm mad, and I'm hungry!
Get the hell out of my way!
Food is your concern.
Very well, then.
Soon you'll never have to worry about eating again.
What's that supposed to mean?
Strawboy!
Whatever you do, don't fight him!
Listen!
That's Magellan, the warden of Impel Down!
He has the power of the Venom Venom Fruit!
He's the last person you ever want to fight!
Make a run for it!
Venom Venom Fruit?
He's poison?
Indeed I am!
You're a bit out of your elements, Straw Hat.
Even though you're a rookie, I expected more from a pirate with a bounty of 300 million.
Especially one who has caused the world government so much trouble.
Speaking of trouble, I can't imagine how you managed to worm your way through security, but here you are.
Rest assured, you will suffer for tarnishing my reputation.
I know why you're here, by the way.
You came to rescue your brother, Portgus D.A., Second Division Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates.
An ambitious endeavor, if a foolish one.
Though struggle as you might, both his fate and yours were sealed the moment you set foot here.
You've had quite the little rampage, but all of that will come to an end now.
And one final thing, I will find out exactly how you broke into my prison.
You will spill every last juicy detail to me.
It's safe now, Luffy.
Wow! That was close!
Even so, I'm afraid that this is as far as I'll be able to accompany you.
They're quite insistent on placing me in those sea prism stone handcuffs.
And once they take my cloak, you'll have nowhere to hide.
I just wish... I wish I could do more to help you, but...
Aw, don't talk like that!
You got me in this place, didn't you? That's more than I could have done alone!
Luffy...
I'll die before I say a word!
Heh! You criminals always spout that sort of nonsense before your interrogation.
But listen, Straw Hat.
When you face the torment I have in store for you, you'll say anything for the mercy of death.
Listen, please!
Magellan's whole body is poisonous, crazy, terrible poison!
If you so much as touch him, you're finished!
You can't beat a guy like that!
I will!
Let's go back the way we came!
To the Pool of Blood!
This way!
Give up on that stupid food and let's hightail it to level five!
There's no escape.
The staircase to level five is protected by three demon guards and their commander.
Huh?
Every exit on this floor has already been accounted for.
There will be no more running.
Now, should I stop them or should I let the warden take the blame?
This is your grave!
No!
I won't believe it!
I can't believe it!
Ah!
Hydra!
What the heck is that?
A venom monster?
The whole thing is poison?
Ah!
You can't!
Why did you..
Don't get in my way!
Didn't you hear me?
You can't fight him..
Listen, if you touch that poison anywhere,
it'll be the last thing you do!
Don't get in my way!
The henry toolbox, you heard me!
What a bunch of crap!
How am I supposed to fight him if I can't even touch him?
You don't.
That's what I'm telling you.
Damn it!
Can't you get me some options here?
Magellan is only aiming for straw boy.
Now gum gum!
I said gum gum!
Lovely pistol!
Crossdresser Gatling!
Ballerina Giant Scythe!
A bit confused, aren't you?
I wonder which one's the real straw hat.
I'm sure it's very difficult to tell us apart.
Hey, Bon.
You forgot the clothes.
Now that I've so cleverly drawn the Hydra's attention,
it's time for you to get away, dear friend.
Here, Hydra, Hydra, Hydra!
Come on!
I'm waiting for you!
I've got you now!
I said there's no escape, and I meant it!
It got bigger!
Uh-oh!
I'll cut my surprise!
Ah!
Gordon Magellan, wait please!
We're still evacuating!
The Warden guy's poisoning his own people!
The Hydra's venom is a paralytic Neurotopsin!
It makes its way through your body, causing horrific pain before you finally die!
It's killing me!
Give me the antidote!
Hurry!
Boss, why?
Stay out of the way when I'm fighting, you damn fools!
You got that?
We're terribly sorry, sir!
Stop chasing me!
I just want to eat!
Help me!
How do you think about food in a time like this?
Either way, you gotta respect a man that knows what he wants!
I admire your bravery, sir!
I love you!
Take a man that knows what he wants!
I admire your bravery, dear friend!
It just sucks that we're both gonna die!
Catch me if you can, Hydra!
I forgot it's really hard!
Oh, right!
One of the heads is gone!
How clever!
You have some of your brother's cunning after all!
Still, this is the end.
Oh, crap!
Get ready!
Here it comes!
Chloroform ball!
That was close!
Put your gas masks on!
Stay clear!
The Warden's in the middle of a battle!
What is this?
Sear gas?
No!
It's Magellan's poison!
Go somewhere else to fight, you bastards!
Who's he up against, anyway?
I don't know.
Maybe that intruder they were talking about.
So, Hell Heat plus poison gas?
Give me a break!
What the?
My eyes itch like crazy!
What's happening to me?
I can't fight!
I can't fight like this!
Whoa!
The Hydra!
Stop moving!
Down the venom road!
Try as you might.
You won't escape from me!
Ugggh!
Get me!
Could I offer you...
..some of this?
Ugggh!
C'mon!
One touch and it's over.
He's melting through the stone.
First the wall, and then you.
We've got to rescue Ace.
Surely even you must know that your death is imminent.
Just like Ace.
Please give me the antidote.
I'm dying.
You mean they were all poisoned by the warden?
Yeah, they got caught up in the crossfire between him and that Straw Hat kid.
At this rate, he'll end up poisoning all of us.
Oh man, I hope not.
Did you hear that?
Sounds like Straw Hat's in a tough fight.
Well, too bad for him, but good for us.
What?
In all the awful things that Impel Down has to offer, Warden Magellan is by far the most deadly.
Right now he's focused on Straw Hat.
So while there are likely guards posted at the staircase to level three, preventing an eventless escape,
at least we can take comfort in knowing we won't face the worst terror.
What I'm saying is, this is our chance.
Strawboy's in trouble.
Worse yet, there's nothing I can do while my dear friend is being subjected to that dreadful poison.
Well, look, there is one thing I can do.
Straw Hat!
Hang in there!
I'm here!
Spinning for you!
What's the use?
That won't help at all.
I'm a fool!
Such a fool!
If I can lay down my life for a friend, then death is a small price to pay.
In the name of all come my way, Vaughn Clay will stand up and fight!
Having said that...
I'm too scared to move!
Ah!
Ouchie!
Look at him.
He's fighting so hard and you can't help him.
Can't you do something?
Calm down.
Think this through.
Swan!
Out of this!
The outcome?
The swan is dead.
I'm pulling my own tail here!
That would never work!
The rose withers and wilts.
Oh, come on!
That's even worse than the other idea!
The rose withers and wilts.
Oh, come on!
That's even worse than the other idea!
I bring you the walls of a winter sky!
I did it!
The garden of all come my way is calling me!
It's useless.
I'm all out of ideas.
I can't even think of a cool way to die!
Straw boy!
My dear friend!
I can't help you!
I can't even think of a cool way to die!
Straw boy!
My dear friend!
I can't help you!
A ugh!
Now come gums!
Now come cums!
Damn!
Warden Magellan guards the most dangerous criminals
in the most infamous prison in the entire world.
He's the lord and master of hell itself.
You're not going to let Strawboy face him alone, are you?
Forgive me.
There's just no way to be him.
I tried to warn you, but you wouldn't listen.
Running is the only answer.
I'm sorry, Strawboy, I'm a coward.
Forgive me.
I'm telling you, we have to make a move
while Magellan is busy with Straw Hat.
Are you out of your mind?
Look how many guards there are down there.
It's nuts.
That doesn't matter.
Just think about it.
They assign the more powerful demon guards
to protect the staircase to level five.
It's more important to them to not let Straw Hat
get down to the lower levels.
Meaning they are the crappiest security they have here.
If we miss this chance,
soon after they'll time their defenses.
Straw Hat will lose at some point.
Once he does, this window is closed.
We must get to level three before that happens.
Actually, maybe you're right.
I've never heard anything about Vice Warden Hannibal
having any Devil Fruit powers.
If I can take out those guards with a muggy ball...
We can do it.
Hannibal can't be that tough, right?
Now you're thinking.
All right, let's do it.
I don't want to stay in this heat one moment longer.
It's now or never.
Ready?
Nothing is going to stop us from getting through.
That's right!
Vice Warden Hannibal!
Look, it's Buggy the Clown and Mr. Three!
Looks like they're trying to get to level three.
We can't let those bastards go any higher.
Let's go!
Now, Muggy!
Can do!
Wait a minute!
Guards, stand down.
Vice Warden, why?
That's right, I'm the Vice Warden and I'm in charge here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here's my chance.
It seems Fortune has finally favored me.
On top of Straw Hat Luffy's invasion,
if these two managed to escape,
I'm sure the officials wouldn't tolerate
this magnitude of incompetence.
Huh?
And since he's the one in charge,
they'll blame Warden Magellan for everything that happened.
After that...
I will be promoted to Warden as I so richly deserve.
Uh, Vice Warden, are you sure you don't want us to stop those two?
Please give us an order!
Anything, sir!
Okay!
Everybody move.
Uh, we've been expecting you,
so please come right this way.
Huh?
You heard me, man. Move it.
Make way.
Don't be rude to our guests.
No way.
Is he serious?
Maybe this is all part of the Vice Warden's secret ploy.
There you are!
Please go right on ahead.
Uh...
Screw a bunch of that!
Can't fool us!
We see right through your sneaky little plot!
There is no way our escape could be that easy.
You could at least make it less obvious!
Huh?
Suck it, Freak Muggy Ball!
Take this, Kendall! Look!
What the hell is wrong with you two idiots?
I said you could go!
Oh, crap.
This isn't good.
I suggest you put an end to this nonsense and submit.
Uh...
I'm gonna rescue my brother.
And we'll escape from here together!
I won't die without even seeing him.
And I'm not gonna let you execute him.
You hear me?
Hm?
What's that smoke?
I don't have time for your tricks.
I'm not getting anywhere.
I can't win without touching you.
I'll make a sacrifice!
You can take my arms, but I won't lose!
Huh?
Why would I need your arms?
You want me to take you apart piece by piece?
Of course, some of the red傷.
I'll cut my hands!
Cut me off!
All right!
Come, come!
Dangerous thunder, die!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This venom proves to be an impenetrable wall chipping away at Luffy's strength and destroying any hope of a counter-attack.
With nowhere to run, Luffy's desperation to save Aix forces him to make a very grim sacrifice as he prepares for one final attack against his adversary.
On the next One Piece, showdown has come. Luffy's desperate last attack. I'm going to be king of the pyre.